Hello everyone welcome back to my channel so
today I am going to do a review on the Naro t-shirt which
I ordered for my husband so let's
see how it is so what is the
first of
[music] I have just zoned the
first one to show you
and this is in XL size so first let's check
how it is
let's show you
this is the first t-shirt which I
ordered its GSM is also good I mean a
little I mean the thickness is good its
not the thin type which is available in the market it is very soft you
can see guys I had ordered this in XL size
and it looks like a soft fabric it is very
nice you can see the close view I liked it
I will like it a
lot Holi and the next one I am
showing you is the next part this one is
in grey colour so this
colour was
grey at least I had ordered grey colour I am
not able to understand whether it was grey
or not so you can see it came in grey it looks
very nice it
gives a very good look and its fully
fitting will also be good and  This print of this in XL size is
also very nice,
it is a fabric print and it is very
nice, you can see it first because many
people get confused, I also had the same thing, when
I was purchasing it first, but I liked it, it is
very nice, I will
give it 10 out of 5 stars and next I
purchased it,
this print is also nice but I am having doubt
that it will not go away after washing,
see guys, the
size seems small, I had purchased XL
but it seems a bit small, this
fabric is nice but
it will not work if it is so cold
because its thickness is a little less and let's see
its inner fabric, see
how is the fabric
and I feel that I will wear it, it looks
good, right guys,
this is the normal one which is used in our planes
here in the doors, it does not feel so cold, it
feels okay, so it is fine for that, I
mean, it may not work in very cold places
and yes, it will bear the normal cold, okay, so guys,
I showed it to all of you  I gave you a
review of all the three items that I had ordered and you can buy the T-shirt, no doubt you can buy it,
I really liked this T-shirt,
its quality is good and the
thickness is also good, so it will be
comfortable to wear, hopefully because it is very
good, I really liked this one, I also liked
this grey one
and the price wise it was kind of okay
because I bought this hoodie for
approximately 1299, so if I had spent
maybe 300 on it, I could have got the HM hoodie,
that too a bit heavy, so
I think if they like it then I will
keep it, if I don't like it
then I will buy it from A, so noro, this was my
shopping, so this is my first shopping,
hopefully you can see and if you want to buy T-shirts
then no doubt you can buy it, I really
liked it, the T-shirt is
also like normally good, but price wise
it's like if you go for 1300 then I do
n't like the thing worth 1300  I found it
okay, it could have been of better quality
and it seems a little thin but the
fabric is very soft,
this one is fine for normal wear, so guys, that's all
for today, I will bring a
different cheese unboxing in the next video.